I'm sorry, what?
Sorry, did you not get all that? It's like a super long title.
Shizuku Tama's my favorite character from Saint Slippery's Academy for Girls, the young ladies of the Humiliation Club debauched Miracle Life!
She's the cutie I want to cosplay as. She's specifically from Slippery Girls 2.
Shizuku Tama's.
Thank you.
I want to be myself at your side, I want to be myself!
The game's even getting an anime, like what?
So, the MC is this principal's grandson, and he enrolls in this all-girls school cause reasons.
Basically, it's your run-of-the-mill harem setup, you get it.
A guy enrolling in an all-girls school is run-of-the-mill?
The super-emotional in-game events are what really get ya.
Assuming you're into hardcore stuff like humiliation play. Or sex slaves.
Sex slaves?
But the sex slaves in Slippery Girls 2 are all doing it for love, so when you look at it that way, it's all pretty vanilla.
Vanilla? Right.
So anyway, the MC is ordered to join a humiliation club by the principal, and all the girls in the club want to-
What is she talking about?
Maybe I'm just not familiar with video games, but this sounds insane to me!
Humiliation club? Sex slaves?
Games like this don't really exist, do they?
Wait, maybe she's messing with me?
Wow, how long are you gonna let me keep talking? I'm obviously kidding, how gullible are you?
Of course. I tend to take people at their word, so it makes sense I wouldn't notice she's making a joke, right?
But if you pick the last option...
No, I take it all back. Kitagawa isn't joking in the slightest.
I mean, look at her eyes.
All that to say, the first Slippery Girls ruled, so once they announced Slippery Girls 2, I was immediately hyped about it.
Cause even if it sucked, it'd still have Shizukutan, but it doesn't suck!
In the beginning, Shizukutan doesn't smile at all.
She's this total ice queen, and you're like, what's this girl's whole deal?
But then as you get more and more events, it's like, wow, so this is who she really is!
I wasn't even halfway into the game yet, and I'd fallen head over heels in love with her.
I was totally and completely obsessed.
And then suddenly...
I realized I wanted to become Shizukutan.
So yeah, you get me?
Not even a little bit.
She's my all-time favorite.
But I do get that she's genuinely having fun telling me all about this.
I mean, she's lit up like the sun.
It's obvious how passionate she is.
It actually turns out to be a super happy ending.
Get it now?
Not quite.
Uh-oh.
Okay, where'd I lose you?
I think I got the basic idea, but I wanted to ask...
What, Shizukutan's birthday?
No, that's not gonna help me.
It just...
It just sounds like Slippery Girls might be, like, an adult game.
Yeah, that's what a rogue means.
But it's totally epic.
Okay.
But isn't that, like, age-restricted content?
Maybe.
But, like, who cares, am I right?
Huh?
I guess I'm just surprised that girls even play games like that, much less enjoy them.
Oh, please, of course we do.
Literally everyone does.
Besides, like...
Hmm?
When you find something that you're really excited about, does gender matter?
Oh.
No, it doesn't!
That's what I'm saying!
All right, let's get rolling.
Sure thing!
I'm looking forward to working with you!
Whoa, Gojo, are you crying right now?
I'm fine.
I guess I better do some research so I can figure out where we need to start.
Oh, I got you.
Let me see.
Aha!
Bum, bum, bum, bum!
A beginner's guide to making cosplay!
Wow.
I didn't know books like this existed.
Oh, yeah.
This thing totally rules.
Look at this!
There's a whole section on how to pick the right fabrics and draft your own patterns!
Yep, yep, yep.
This thing is super handy.
Wow.
And they even break down how to use a sewing machine.
Yeah, it's great!
She has a book that's crystal clear, and I still couldn't...
I'll do this on my own.
I'm embarrassed.
All right.
We can talk about materials later.
We should start with your measurements.
Okay, let's do that now!
Uh, no.
It's already getting pretty late, and I have stuff to do this weekend.
Why don't we meet up again on Monday?
Right.
Monday works.
Hey, Gojo.
What's up?
You're the best.
I'll see you on Monday, okay?
All right.
Knock, knock.
You're going to bed already?
That's unusual.
Hmm.
I'm gonna go buy a sewing machine tomorrow, so you don't need to open up the shop.
Works for me.
Better take a bath before you conk out.
Yep.
That really happened.
I really want to do right by her.
Yes, I'm coming.
I'll be right there.
I'm sorry, but we're close to the...
Hey!
How's it going?
What are you doing here?
And how did you know where I lived?
Don't be a doof.
There was no freaking way I was gonna wait through the whole weekend to become Shizuku-tan.
So, I just searched for Gojo plus Hina dolls, and yay!
There you were.
Someone's proactive.
So, can I come in or what?
Like, right now?
No.
Well, I mean...
V-T-dubs, this is for you.
Huh?
Wow.
Thank you.
You didn't have to do that for...
Oops, I'm inside.
Hey, wait just a second!
Oh.
Is your room upstairs, Gojo?
Yeah?
I want to see.
Wait!
No!
Oh.
Wait, wait, wait.
This is totally your room, isn't it?
Kitagawa.
Oh.
Yep, this looks like a Gojo kind of room to me.
Come on, put your futon away, Nessie.
Are these for the dolls?
I can't believe you can paint with these itty-bitty little brushes.
Damn.
Oh, don't worry.
I won't touch them.
But seriously, these are so tiny.
Oh, no.
My heart's beating so loud that I can't hear a word she's saying.
I mean, the only person who's ever been in my bedroom is my own grandfather.
But now there's a girl!
And it's Kitagawa!
This is bad.
Nothing like this has ever happened to me before.
What am I supposed to do?
Calm down, Wakanakojo.
You can do this.
Just chill out.
I need to get a grip.
I need to make sure I'm not rude to her.
Hello, Earth to Gojo.
Hi!
Sorry!
Would you mind repeating that?
Yeah, I was just saying.
Do you want to hurry up?
And do it?
Uh...
Take my measurements, duh.
You're the one who said we had to do that first, so come on.
Let's get measuring.
Right, I wanted to bring that up.
I think you might actually need to find someone else to do that part for you.
Wait, are you for real?
Do you not want to do this anymore?
No.
I mean, yes, I do.
It's just...
In the book I borrowed yesterday, it said that for measurements...
You have to be in your underwear.
Ah, so that's what you're worried about.
Yeah, no problem.
Hey, let's not be too hasty!
Ta-da!
I wore a bathing suit.
So relax.
I figured you might get all flustered about this part.
But then I thought of this, and I was like,
Whoa, dude!
I'm a genius!
Well?
Now it's not awkward, right?
Gojo?
Hey, dude.
You good?
No!
I don't need you to touch me right now!
Whoa, freak out!
Sorry!
Okay, I guess we'll start with your head measurement.
Please be patient with me.
Sure thing!
Here.
Does it help if I close my eyes?
Calm down.
Breathe.
Concentrate.
And whatever you do, do not actually touch Kitagawa.
Take care.
Whoa, are you okay?
That wasn't a good sound.
Yeah, I'm fine.
Don't worry.
I need to measure the width of your shoulders.
So, could you turn around for me?
Uh-huh.
What a nightmare.
I can't keep my composure when I'm facing her.
But if I have her turn away from me, then maybe...
Nope!
That's actually worse!
My hair's probably in the way, huh?
How's this?
Hey, uh, may I ask you a question?
Hmm?
We're practically strangers, but you're in a bathing suit in my room, so...
Aren't...
Aren't you even a little bit embarrassed?
What?
Embarrassed?
No way!
I mean, if I'm gonna become Shizuku-tan, then we need to follow that book to the letter.
Hmm?
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa!
What the heck was that sound?
Uh, is everything okay?
Right.
What are you doing?
Of course!
This project means so much to her.
It's rude for me to have any indecent thoughts.
Everything's just fine!
You've nothing to worry about!
I don't know, I kind of feel like I do.
She's relying on me here.
So she deserves absolutely everything I have to give.
Heart and soul.
I just need to concentrate on doing the work to the best of my ability.
Everything look okay?
Yep.
Oh, hold up.
Before I forget, would you mind helping me measure my feet, too?
Your feet?
Sure, but I can't make shoes from scratch.
I thought we could just buy some for us to use as a vase and build around them.
Right, but even then I have problems.
Some heels and stuff can start hurting, even if they're the same size as all my other shoes.
Well, that could just be an issue of circumference or something.
Like here?
Yeah, but we'll get your width, too.
Hang tight for a sec, okay?
I'll go grab a chair for you.
Wait, how about I just...
Check it out.
Totally perfect, yeah?
No!
No, it is not!
Well, you know, I mean, I have it washed.
It's, you know, it's...
It's dirty, okay?
Doesn't bother me any.
It's all good.
See?
No!
I'm begging you, please get off that filthy thing immediately and let me get to a real chair!
But why?
It's fine.
You're not listening to me!
It's not fine!
You'll get dirty, please!
The longer we argue about this, the less measuring we get done.
I'll...
I'll run and get you a chair.
It won't take more than a second.
Please.
I'm so sorry.
Gojo.
Relax already.
It's fine.
Okay.
I see.
Cool.
I'll have to remember this next time I shop.
Okay.
Moving right along.
Next up is...
My bust!
I should probably tie up my hair for this, too.
Great.
Here we go.
Let's do it.
Sorry.
You're not saying...
I'm supposed to measure them, are you?
Yeah, of course I am.
I mean, who else is gonna do it?
You could do it.
Are you kidding me?
When you do it by yourself, you have to lean, like, way forward.
And I wind up with a different result pretty much every time.
It's actually way harder than you'd think.
So, come on.
Get over here, Gojo.
Do...
Do I have to?
Huh?
Yes, you do.
I don't get why you're so constantly freaked out.
I...
I just...
I really don't think I should.
The sooner you do it, the sooner it's done.
And besides, my arms are killing me.
Right!
I'm so sorry.
I'll measure them right o...
She's so close!
This is exactly why I didn't want to do this.
She's just so...
No, no, no, no, no, shut up!
Don't think about anything else!
You're only getting her measurements.
That's it.
That's it!
Just concentrate on making her close.
You got this.
Right.
I need you to lower your arms and stand up straight for me, please.
Sure thing.
Concentrate.
Concentrate!
I know, right?
Crouching like that for too long is rough on your knees.
But whatever position makes you the happiest is fine by me.
I want to die.
I think we're done.
Woohoo!
But hey, as long as we're still here, why don't we grab my inseam and bust point too?
No.
This again?
How am I supposed to make the perfect boob bag if I don't have the right measurements?
Um, boob bag?
Yeah.
I really want to give this part some extra love, so I'm going to need you to psych yourself up.
I'm sorry, but I, I just can't.
Oh, what's your deal?
Seriously, why can't you?
Just, how, how, how am I supposed to, how am I supposed to instinctively know where your nipples are?
You see, I can't, okay?
Well, hey.
Huh?
You could find out.
Oh my gosh, I'm totally kidding.
You don't have to freeze up like that, you know?
But, yeah, you're right.
I can't show you those without it getting real awkward.
I'm sorry.
We good?
Here, give me the measuring tape and I'll take care of it myself.
Thank you.
I'm sorry.
Okay.
Let's see.
So it's just straight across from here to here.
Or wait, not the outside, the middle.
20 centimeters!
20 centimeters.
How is it that one number can blast everything out of my brain?
And that just leaves the inseam, right?
Right.
At least I don't have to look at her face for this one, so I shouldn't be as nervous.
I'm sort of done with myself.
I keep getting all flustered and panicky.
Talk about lame.
I wish I could be more like her.
It's like she's never lost her cool even once in her life.
Sorry, did you just say something?
I didn't mean to zone out.
I got lost in thought for a second, so I must have missed...
Kitagawa?
Huh?
You...
You're bright red.
Huh?
No, I...
Am I...
Hey, don't get the wrong idea or anything.
I'm just...
Hmm?
Oh!
Did it get too hot in here for you?
I'm so sorry I didn't notice sooner.
I'll go turn on the AC.
Got warm out early this year, huh?
I guess.
That's the last of them.
Yay!
Can I get dressed now?
Yep.
Oh, but first...
Huh?
Do you have references from Slippery Girls?
I'm gonna draft patterns, so we'd help to see the outfits in the game.
Heck yeah!
Do I ever?
Here, check it.
Boom!
Slippery Girls 1 and 2.
Here.
Oh.
Perfect.
Thank you so much.
T-two of them?
I thought that maybe the second one would be enough, but you really need to play the first
one to understand all the lore.
Right.
And we got plenty of weekend left, so give them a shot.
I promise they're super cute.
Yikes, you okay?
Uh, I-I-I didn't mean to interrupt you while you were changing.
No, that's fine, but...
You good?
Stomachache, or...?
No, I'm completely fine.
Please don't worry.
It's literally just a bathing suit.
I'm so pathetic.
Wakana, I'm back.
I got the new sewing ma-
Ah!
Oh, wait, what?
You're watching me?
Oh!
If I do this...
Hey, Gramps.
Welcome back.
Dinner's ready downstairs.
Uh, okay.
Uh, I bought the new sewing machine.
Nice.
Thank you.
Well, I suppose he is at that age.
This sort of thing is natural, right?
But why does he look so serious in there?
I see.
So that's how it looks from the back.
And he's taking notes?
Hmm...
She'll be fine.
She likes it.
See you next time.